{
    "id": "2c5d870f6ba94436a2374ac9476f2a6a",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Wild animals ……………… in forests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "are living"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… for California next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "am leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Sita cannot come out to play now, as she ………………… her mother in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "helps",
                "is helping"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. Bangalore every summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "are visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "An honest person always ……………….. the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "speaks",
                "is speaking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………….. his lunch. Please wait.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "is having",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There are some birds that …………….. every year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "migrate",
                "are migrating"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The rain …………….. from the clouds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "falls",
                "is falling"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A person who ………………. provisions is known as a grocer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sells",
                "is selling"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………. with our eyes …………… with our ears and  …………… with our nose.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see, hear, smell",
                "are seeing, are hearing, are smelling"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}